Guide to the Forest Hills Gardens (New York, N.Y.) Records, 1900-1970, 1911-1919 (bulk)
Forest Hills Gardens (New York, N.Y.) Records, 1900-1970, 1911-1919 (bulk)
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Forest Hills Gardens (New York, N.Y.) records, 1900-1970 1911-1919
2495
Forest Hills Gardens (New York, N.Y.)
8.6 cubic ft.
Brochures, specifications, declarations of restrictions, and blueprints.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Brochures, specifications, declarations of restrictions, and blueprints of homes in Forest Hills Gardens.
ORGANIZATIONAL HISTORY
Forest Hills Gardens is a planned residential community which was developed by the Russell Sage Foundation in 1908. Laid out on 175 acres in Queens, New York, the community's site plan was designed by Frederick Law Olmsted, Jr.; many of the houses were designed by Grosvenor Atterbury.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Brochures, specifications, declarations of restrictions, and blueprints of homes in Forest Hills Gardens.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Forest Hills Gardens (New York, N.Y.)
Subjects:
Architecture.; City planning.; Community development, Urban.
Places:
Queens County (N.Y.)
Form and Genre Terms:
Blueprints.; Brochures.; Specifications.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Abbreviations used in the collection
1st = First Floor Plan
2nd = Second Floor Plan
2nd, A. = Second Floor Plan, Attic Plan,
2nd, R. Pl. = Second Floor Plan, Roof Plan
3rd = Third Floor Plan
A. = Attic Plan
B. = Basement Floor Plan
B. 1st = Basement Floor Plan, First Floor Plan
B. Pl. = Block Plan
Bldg. = Buildings
C. = Cellar Plan
C. Sc. = Cross Sections
D. = Details
E. = East Elevation
Ele. = Elevation
En. Ele. = End Elevation
Ext. = Exterior Elevation
F. = Front Elevation
Fou. Pl. = Foundation Plan
G. = Grounds
Gar. = Garage
Grd. Pl. = Grading Plan
H. Pl. = Heating Plan
Int. Ele. = Interior Elevation
L. Sc. = Longitudinal Sections
Lf. Ele. = Left Elevation
Lf. Sd. = Left Side Elevation
N. = North Elevation
P. Pl. = Plot Plan
Plb. Pl. = Plumbing Plan
Plb. Sc. = Plumbing Section
Prelim. Sk. = Preliminary Sketch
R. = Rear Elevation
R. Pl. = Roof Plan
Rt. Ele. = Right Elevation
Rt. Sd. = Right Side Elevation
S., S. Ele. = South Elevation
Sc. = Sections
Sd. Ele. = Side Elevation
St. Ele. = Street Elevation
Sta. Sc. = Staircase Section
T. Sc. = Transverse Section
Topo. Mp. = Topographical Map
W. = West Elevation
RELATED MATERIAL
See also Forest Hills Gardens Corporation Records, ( #2775).
CONTAINER LIST
- Link to a paper finding aid.
- I-F 25 (I-F25 -64), 1924 - 1925 (Map-case Folder 56)
  Project Description: Residence for Louis Galluci
  Architect: Chas M. Lobejager
  Drawings List: Cellar Plan, First Floor Plan, Second Floor Plan, Roof Plan, South Elevation, West Elevation, North Elevation, East Elevation, Sketch of South (front) Elevation, End Elevation
  Other Details: Multiple copies of some drawings
- I-F 36, Undated (Map-case Folder 67)
  Project Description: House
  Architect: G. Atterbury
  Drawings List: Block Plan
  Other Details: Faces Road No. 38
- I-F 42-45, Undated (Map-case Folder 67)
  Project Description: Houses
- I-F 46- I-F 49, 1911-1912 (Map-case Folder 67)
- I-F 47, I-F 48, 1911-1912 (Map-case Folder 67)
- I-F-46, I-F 47, I-F 48, 1911-1912 (Map-case Folder 57)
  Architect: S. F. H. Company, Landscaping - Olmsted Bros., Group XII Drawings
  Drawings List: Attic Plan, Plan of Flower Box, Elevations of Living, Dining and Bed rooms, Details of Lattice Work. Elevation of Dining room, Dining room Interior, Elevation of Entrance Hall, Section through Main Wing, Parquet Flooring, Details of Stairs, Staircase Section, Misc. Details, Staircase Hall Interior, 5 plates - Chimney Details, Details of Finished Fireplace, Dormer Windows, Living room Interior, Kitchen and Pantry Dressers, Details for China Closet, 2 plates - Hoods over Front and Rear Entrances, 2 plates - Details of steps, Grading Plan, Plan for location of Garage and Revision of Lot Lines
  Other Details: Corner Markwood Rd + Greenway north, 4 house group
- I-F 51, Undated (Map-case Folder 67)
  Other Details: Line A (street) almost across from Road 39
- I-F 52, Undated (Map-case Folder 67)
  Project Description: Detached House
  Other Details: NOTE: A drawing of façade appears on p.21 of Pamphlet no. 1. - KJ, 3/6/80
- I-F 91, Undated (Map-case Folder 67)
  Other Details: Ingram Street, Puritan Avenue shown on drawing
- I-F 92, I-F 93, I-F 94, Undated (Map-case Folder 67)
- I-F 95, Undated (Map-case Folder 67)
- I-F 96, Undated (Map-case Folder 67)
- I-F 97, I-F 98, Undated (Map-case Folder 67)
- I-F 99, Undated (Map-case Folder 67)
  Other Details: Ingram Street, between 199 and 200
- I-F 100, Undated (Map-case Folder 67)
  Other Details: Ingram Street, between 198 and 199
- I-F 101, I-F 102, Undated (Map-case Folder 67)
- I-F 103, Undated (Map-case Folder 67)
  Other Details: Ingram Street, near corner Ascan Avenue, near # 198
- I-F 112, I-F 113, I-F 114, Undated (Map-case Folder 67)
  Other Details: Puritan Avenue and corner of Ingram Street
- I-F 232, 1911 (Map-case Folder 1)
  Project Description: House for Mrs. Carrie M. Jessup
  Drawings List: Basement Floor Plan, First Floor Plan, Cross Section, Plumbing Section, Longitudinal Section
- I-F 233, 1911 (Map-case Folder 1)
  Project Description: House for P. B. Cole
  Drawings List: Topographical Map - Block 35, Basement Floor Plan, First Floor Plan, Attic Plan, Second Floor Plan, South Elevation, West Elevation, East Elevation, North Elevation, Longitudinal Section, Cross Section
  Other Details: Blueprints, 40"wX22"l
- I-F 234, 1911 (Map-case Folder 1)
  Project Description: House for C. E. Kloetzer
  Drawings List: Topographical Map, Basement Floor Plan, First Floor Plan, Second Floor Plan, Third Floor Plan, Left Side Elevation, Rear Elevation, Details of Iron Balcony
- I-F 235, 1912 (Map-case Folder 2)
  Project Description: House for J. J. Crawford
  Drawings List: Topographical Map Block #22 - Lots 53 & 54, First Floor Plan, Basement Floor Plan, Second Floor Plan, Attic Plan, Southwest Elevation, Front Elevation, North East Elevation, Rear Elevation, Cross Section, Longitudinal Section
- I-F 237, 1911, 1919 (Map-case Folder 2)
  Project Description: Wm. Jay Leonard
  Architect: Albro & Lindeberg, Architects
  Drawings List: New Front Terrace, Basement Floor Plan, First Floor Plan, Second Floor Plan, Third Floor Plan, Front Elevation, Left Side Elevation, Rear Elevation, Right Side Elevation, Cross Section, Longitudinal Section, Plumbing Section
- I-F 238, 1911-1912 (Map-case Folder 3)
  Project Description: House for John J. Sheanan
  Architect: F. J. Sterner, Architect
  Drawings List: Preliminary Sketch, Basement Floor Plan, First Floor Plan, Second Floor Plan, Roof Plan, Front Elevation, Left Side Elevation, Right Side Elevation, Rear Elevation, Cross Section, Plumbing Section, Longitudinal Section
- I-F 240, 1912 (Map-case Folder 3)
  Project Description: House for T. C. Jones
  Drawings List: Block Plan #33, Basement Floor Plan, First Floor Plan, Second Floor Plan, Roof Plan, North West Elevation, South West Elevation, North East Elevation, South East Elevation, Cross Section, Longitudinal Section
  Other Details: Duplicates sent to owner: Nancy Srodin on 12/21/1993
- I-F 241, 1911 (Map-case Folder 4)
  Project Description: House for Mrs. E. J. Smith
  Drawings List: Plan no. 3342 - Contour Map, Basement Floor Plan, First Floor Plan, Second Floor Plan, Roof Plan, West Elevation, North Elevation, South Elevation, East Elevation, Transverse Section, Longitudinal Section
- I-F 242, 1911-1912 (Map-case Folder 4)
  Project Description: House for Mrs. W. P. Hooper
  Drawings List: Basement Floor Plan, First Floor Plan, Second Floor Plan, Attic Plan, Roof Plan, Front Elevation, End Elevation, Rear Elevation, Longitudinal Section, Cross Section
- I-F 243, 1911 (Map-case Folder 5)
  Project Description: House for M. Worth Colwell
  Drawings List: Topographical Map Lots 1/2 28, 29, 30; Basement Floor Plan, First Floor Plan, Second Floor Plan, Roof Plan, Front Elevation, Left Side Elevation, Right Side Elevation, Rear Elevation, Plumbing Section, Cross Section
- I-F 245, 1913 (Map-case Folder 5)
  Project Description: House for F. R. Getz
  Drawings List: Basement Floor Plan, First Floor Plan, Second Floor Plan, Attic Plan, Front Elevation, Right Side Elevation, Rear Elevation, Left Side Elevation, Construction, Plumbing Section
- I-F 247, 1912 (Map-case Folder 6)
  Project Description: House for Harold Martin
  Drawings List: Car Garage, Basement Floor Plan, First Floor Plan, Second Floor Plan, Third Floor Plan, Front Elevation, Left Side Elevation, Rear Elevation, Right Side Elevation, Cross Section, Longitudinal Section
- I-F 248, 1911 (Map-case Folder 6)
  Project Description: House for M. B. Pope
  Drawings List: Topographical Map Lots 31, 32 1/2, 33, Basement Floor Plan, First Floor Plan, Second Floor Plan, Roof Plan, Rear Elevation, Side Elevations, Front Elevation, Transverse Section, Longitudinal Section
  Other Details: Upton Street, Block #38
- I-F 251, 1912 (Map-case Folder 7)
  Project Description: House for Dr. R. W. Waddell
  Drawings List: Basement Floor Plan, First Floor Plan, Second Floor Plan, Attic Plan, North West Elevation, Front Elevation, South East Elevation, Rear Elevation, Plumbing Section, Longitudinal Section
- I-F 252, 1912 (Map-case Folder 7)
  Project Description: House for F. Hagens
  Drawings List: Basement Floor Plan, First Floor Plan, Second Floor Plan, Attic Plan, Roof Plan, Front Elevation, Rear Elevation, Side Elevations, Plumbing Section, Cross Section
- I-F 253, 1912 (Map-case Folder 8)
  Project Description: House for A. D. Anderson
  Drawings List: Basement Floor Plan, First Floor Plan, Second Floor Plan, Third Floor Plan, Front Elevation, Side Elevation, Rear Elevation, Side Elevation, Garage all Elevations, Cross Section, Plumbing Section
- I-F 255, 1912 (Map-case Folder 8)
  Project Description: House for F. C. Kay
  Drawings List: Basement Floor Plan, First Floor Plan, Second Floor Plan, Third Floor Plan, Rear Elevation, Side Elevations, Front Elevation, Section
- I-F 256, 1913 (Map-case Folder 9)
  Project Description: Company's Studio House
  Architect: Sage Foundation Homes Co.
  Drawings List: Basement Floor Plan, First Floor Plan, Second Floor Plan, Front Elevation, Rear Elevation, Right Side Elevation, Left Side Elevation, Section, Longitudinal Section, Plumbing Section
  Other Details: Multiple copies of some drawings, 80 Slocum Crescent
- I-F 257, 1912 (Map-case Folder 9)
  Project Description: John Ihlder
  Drawings List: Basement Floor Plan, First Floor Plan, Second Floor Plan, Third Floor Plan, Front Elevation, Side Elevation, Rear Elevation, Cross Section, Longitudinal Section
- I-F 258, 1912-1913 (Map-case Folder 10)
  Project Description: House for E. G. Trowbridge
  Drawings List: Foundation Plan, Basement Floor Plan, First Floor Plan, Second Floor Plan, Attic Plan, Front Elevation, Side Elevation, Rear Elevation, Side Elevation, Section, Longitudinal Section, Plumbing Section
- I-F 258, 1919 (Map-case Folder 10)
  Project Description: Mr. T. C. Barnes
  Drawings List: Floor Plan, One Car Garage, Two Car Garage
- I-F 262, 1912 (Map-case Folder 10)
  Project Description: House for Miss A. G. Price
  Drawings List: Basement Floor Plan, First Floor Plan, Second Floor Plan, Attic Plan, North West Elevation, Front Elevation, South East Elevation, Rear Elevation, Longitudinal Section, Plumbing Section
- I-F 263, 1912 (Map-case Folder 11)
  Project Description: House for Herman Rountree
  Drawings List: Basement Floor Plan, First Floor Plan, Second Floor Plan, Third Floor Plan, Front Elevation, Side Elevations, Rear Elevation, Section, Plumbing Section
- I-F 266, 1912 (Map-case Folder 11)
  Project Description: House for J. J. Finnegan
  Drawings List: Basement Floor Plan, First Floor Plan, Second Floor Plan, Third Floor Plan, Front Elevation, West Elevation, Rear Elevation, East Elevation, Cross Section, Plumbing Section
- I-F 267, 1913 (Map-case Folder 12)
  Project Description: House for Walter S. Mayer, Esq.
  Architect: Robert M. Farrington, Architect
  Drawings List: Cellar Plan, First Floor Plan, Second Floor Plan, Attic Plan, Roof Plan, Front Elevation, West Elevation, Continental Avenue Elevation, Olive Place Elevation, South Elevation, Garden Elevation, Rear Elevation
- I-F 267, 1913 (Map-case Folder 12)
  Project Description: Garage for Walter S. Mayer, Esq.
  Drawings List: Plan, Elevation, Section
- I-F 268, 1912 (Map-case Folder 12)
  Project Description: House for Mrs. H. L. Young
  Drawings List: Basement Floor Plan, First Floor Plan, Second Floor Plan, Third Floor Plan, Front Elevation, Left Side Elevation, Rear Elevation, Right Side Elevation, Plumbing Section, Cross Section
- I-F 269, 1912 (Map-case Folder 13)
  Project Description: House for W. R. Hulbert
  Drawings List: Basement Floor Plan, First Floor Plan, Second Floor Plan, Third Floor Plan, Rear Elevation, Side Elevations, Front Elevation, Plumbing Section, Cross Section
- I-F 272, 1919 (Map-case Folder 13)
  Project Description: Two Car Garage for Mrs. J. R. Woodrough
  Drawings List: All Elevations
- I-F 272, 1912 (Map-case Folder 13)
  Project Description: House for A. C. Well
  Drawings List: Basement Floor Plan, First Floor Plan, Second Floor Plan, Third Floor Plan, Front Elevation, Right Side Elevation, Rear Elevation, Left Side Elevation, Cross Section, Longitudinal Section
  Other Details: (dated based on # 273 and stamp on reverse)
- I-F 273, 1912 (Map-case Folder 14)
  Project Description: House for A. K. Hanks
  Drawings List: Basement Floor Plan, First Floor Plan, Second Floor Plan, Third Floor Plan, Front Elevation, Right Side Elevation, Rear Elevation, Left Side Elevation, Cross Section, Plumbing Section
- I-F 275, 1912 (Map-case Folder 14)
  Project Description: House for Miss Oehler
  Drawings List: Foundation Plan, First Floor Plan, Second Floor Plan, Attic Plan, Front Elevation, Right Side Elevation, Rear Elevation, Left Side Elevation, Plumbing Section, Cross Section
- I-F 276, 1912 (Map-case Folder 15)
  Project Description: House for P. H. Eder
  Drawings List: Basement Floor Plan, First Floor Plan, Second Floor Plan, Third Floor Plan, Front Elevation, South West Side Elevation, Rear Elevation, North East Side Elevation, Plumbing Section, Cross Section
- I-F 286, c. 1918 (approved) (Map-case Folder 15)
  Project Description: House for H. H. Buckley
  Drawings List: First Floor Plan, Second Floor Plan, Third Floor Plan, Front Elevation, Left Side Elevation, Rear Elevation, Right Side Elevation, Longitudinal Section, Plumbing Section, Garage - All Elevations
- I-F 298, 1913 (Map-case Folder 16)
  Project Description: House for Edward Van Wagenen, Esq.
  Architect: Nelson Van Wagenen, Architect
  Drawings List: Cellar Plan, Second Floor Plan, Attic Plan, North West Elevation, South East Elevation, South West Elevation, North East Elevation - 2 plates
- I-F 301, 1912 (Map-case Folder 16)
  Project Description: House for Miss Lillian Dyvenor Rice
  Drawings List: Foundation Plan for Garage, Basement Floor Plan, First Floor Plan, Second Floor Plan, Third Floor Plan, Front Elevation, Right Side Elevation, Rear Elevation, Left Side Elevation, Cross Section, Plumbing Section
- I-F 302, 1912 (Map-case Folder 17)
  Project Description: House for Charles Ed. Stowe
  Drawings List: Basement Floor Plan, First Floor Plan, Second Floor Plan, Third Floor Plan, Rear Elevation, Front Elevation, Left Side Elevation, Right Side Elevation, Section
- I-F 303, 1912 (Map-case Folder 17)
  Project Description: House for Albert Stotler
  Drawings List: Basement Floor Plan, First Floor Plan, Second Floor Plan, Attic Plan, Front Elevation, Right Side Elevation, Rear Elevation, Left Side Elevation, Plumbing Section, Cross Section
- I-F 304, 1912-1914 (Map-case Folder 18)
  Project Description: House for C. H. Schammel
  Drawings List: Block Plan, Basement Floor Plan, First Floor Plan, Second Floor Plan, Third Floor Plan, Front Elevation, Rear Elevation, Left Side Elevation, Right Side Elevation, No Title, Cross Section, Plumbing Section, Sketches
  Other Details: Multiple copies of some drawings, Additional Revised drawings
- I-F 304, 1912 (Map-case Folder 18)
  Architect: Olmsted Brothers
  Drawings List: Grounds Plan
- I-F 305, 1912-1913 (Map-case Folder 18)
  Project Description: House for A. E. McFarlane
  Drawings List: Basement Floor Plan, First Floor Plan, Second Floor Plan, Attic Plan, Rear Elevation, Side Elevation, Left Side Elevation, Front Elevation, Longitudinal Section, Plumbing Section
  Other Details: Two copies of drawings
- I-F 306, 1912 (Map-case Folder 19)
  Project Description: House for Dr. A. Latham Baker
  Drawings List: Preliminary Sketch of House, Preliminary Sketch of Second Floor, Basement Floor Plan, First Floor Plan, Second Floor Plan, Third Floor Plan, Porch and Left Side Elevation, Front Elevation, Right Side Elevation, Rear Elevation, Left Side Elevation
- I-F 307, 1912-1913 (Map-case Folder 19)
  Project Description: House of F. A. Stone
  Architect: John Allerken, Architect
  Drawings List: 2 Plates of Revised Kitchen Pantry and New Sleeping Porch
- I-F 307, 1912-1913 (Map-case Folder 19)
  Project Description: House for J. A. Meeker
  Drawings List: Basement Floor Plan, First Floor Plan, Second Floor Plan, Third Floor Plan, Front Elevation, Right Side Elevation, Rear Elevation, Left Side Elevation, Plumbing Section, Cross Section, 3 Plates of Dining Room, 3 Plates of Living Room Mantel
- I-F 312, 1912 (Map-case Folder 20)
  Project Description: Company House
  Drawings List: Basement Floor Plan, First Floor Plan, Second Floor Plan, Third Floor Plan, Front Elevation, Right Side Elevation, Rear Elevation, Left Side Elevation, Section, Plumbing Section
- I-F 313, 1912 (Map-case Folder 20)
  Project Description: House for F. W. Goudy
  Drawings List: Basement Floor Plan, First Floor Plan, Second Floor Plan, Roof Plan, Front Elevation, Right Side Elevation, Left Side Elevation, Rear Elevation, Plumbing Section, Cross Section
- I-F 318, 1912-1913 (Map-case Folder 21)
  Project Description: House for H. P. Daniels
  Drawings List: Preliminary Sketch, Basement Floor Plan, Foundation Plan, Cellar Plan, First Floor Plan, Second Floor Plan, Third Floor Plan, Attic Plan, Rear Elevation, Front Elevation, Right Side Elevation, Side Elevation, Windows, Suggestion for front door Hardware, Longitudinal Section, Plumbing Section
  Other Details: Multiple copies of some drawings, Revised and Corrected
- I-F 321, 1913-1914 (Map-case Folder 21)
  Project Description: House for C. L. C. Earle
  Drawings List: Basement Floor Plan, First Floor Plan, Second Floor Plan, Third Floor Plan, Front Elevation, North Side Elevation, South Side Elevation, Rear Elevation, Longitudinal Section, Plumbing Section, Details of Trellis
  Other Details: Three copies of drawings
- I-F 323, 1913-1915 (Map-case Folder 22)
  Project Description: House for H. Mullen
  Architect: Albro Lindenberg
  Drawings List: Basement Floor Plan, First Floor Plan, Second Floor Plan, Third Floor Plan, Front Elevation, Rear Elevation, Side Elevation, Longitudinal Section, Plumbing Section
- I-F 324, 1913 (Map-case Folder 22)
  Project Description: House for J. Rea
  Drawings List: Grading Plan, Basement Floor Plan, First Floor Plan, Second Floor Plan, Third Floor Plan, Front Elevation, Side Elevations, Rear Elevation, Plumbing Section, Longitudinal Section
- I-F 326, 1913 (Map-case Folder 23)
  Project Description: House for S. W. Hart
  Architect: Allen & Williams, Architects
  Drawings List: Cellar Plan, First Floor Plan, Second Floor Plan, Rear Elevation, Front Elevation, East Elevation, West Elevation
  Other Details: 111 Whitson Street
- I-F 328, 1913 (Map-case Folder 23)
  Project Description: House for Howard Duff, Esq.
  Architect: Eugene Schoen
  Drawings List: Block Plan, Cellar Plan, First Floor Plan, Second Floor Plan, Attic Plan, South Elevation, West Elevation, North Elevation, East Elevation, Section
- I-F 330, 1913 (Map-case Folder 24)
  Drawings List: Sketch of the House, First Floor Plan, Second Floor Plan
- I-F 332, 1913 (Map-case Folder 24)
  Project Description: House for Dr. Thompson Sweeny
  Drawings List: Basement Floor Plan, First Floor Plan, Second Floor Plan, Third Floor Plan, Front Elevation, Right Side Elevation, Rear Elevation, Left Side Elevation, Plumbing Section, Cross Section
- I-F 349, 1913 (Map-case Folder 25)
  Architect: Unknown
  Drawings List: Basement Floor Plan, First Floor Plan, Second Floor Plan, Front Elevation, Right Side Elevation, Rear Elevation, Left Side Elevation, Plumbing Section
- I-F 417, 1915 (Map-case Folder 25)
  Project Description: House for Arthur M. Wolfson, Esq.
  Architect: Herbert M. Baer, Architect
  Drawings List: Cellar Plan, First Floor Plan, Second Floor Plan, Front Elevation, Rear Elevation, Side Elevation, Section, Front Door Details
- I-F 420, 1914 (Map-case Folder 26)
  Project Description: House for Mrs. A. D. Miller
- I-F 421, 1914 (Map-case Folder 26)
  Project Description: House for R. Angell
  Drawings List: Basement Floor Plan, First Floor Plan, Second Floor Plan, Third Floor Plan, Front Elevation, Right Side Elevation, Rear Elevation, Left Side Elevation, Staircase Section, Plumbing Section
- I-F 422, I-F 423, 1913 (Map-case Folder 27)
  Project Description: Studies for Trabert House
  Drawings List: Preliminary Sketch of: Side Elevation, Front Elevation, Side Elevation, Rear Elevation, Foundation Plan, First Floor Plan, Third Floor Plan (revised)
- I-F 423, 1922 (Map-case Folder 27)
  Project Description: House for Howard Clark Barber
  Architect: Derby & Robinson, Architects
  Drawings List: Plot Plan, Basement Floor Plan, First Floor Plan, Second Floor Plan, West Elevation, East Elevation, North Elevation, Porch Section, South Elevation, Living Room Section, Dining Room Section
- I-F 426, Undated (Map-case Folder 28)
  Project Description: House on lot
- I-F 430, 1914 (Map-case Folder 28)
  Project Description: House for G. J. Simons
  Drawings List: Basement Floor Plan, First Floor Plan, Second Floor Plan, Third Floor Plan, Front Elevation, Right Side Elevation, Left Side Elevation, Plumbing Section, Cross Section
- I-F 436, 1914 (Map-case Folder 29)
  Project Description: House for Arthur Wright
  Drawings List: Basement Floor Plan, First Floor Plan, Second Floor Plan, Front Elevation, Right Side Elevation, Rear Elevation, Left Side Elevation, Plumbing Section, Cross Section
  Other Details: NEED TO CHECK THE DRAWINGS ONCE WE GET THEM BACK
- I-F 439, 1914 (Map-case Folder 29)
  Drawings List: Basement Floor Plan, First Floor Plan, Second Floor Plan, Third Floor Plan, Front Elevation, Right Side Elevation, Rear Elevation, Left Side Elevation, Longitudinal Section, Plumbing Section
- I-F 445, 1914 (Map-case Folder 30)
  Project Description: House for F. G. Cooper
- I-F 449, 1914 (Map-case Folder 30)
- I-F 450, 1914 (Map-case Folder 31)
- I-F 456, 1913 (Map-case Folder 31)
  Project Description: House on the Corner of Middlemay Place and the Green
  Drawings List: Second Floor Plan, Third Floor Plan, Elevation on Village Green, Elevation on Middelmay Place
- I-F 464, 1914 (Map-case Folder 31)
- I-F 512-513, 1915 (Map-case Folder 32)
  Project Description: Grade Plan for Mr. Hillman
  Architect: Olmsted Brothers; Craftman, Architect
  Drawings List: Grade Plan
- I-F 513, 1915 (Map-case Folder 32)
  Project Description: House for Mr. Hillman
  Drawings List: Basement Floor Plan, First Floor Plan, Second Floor Plan, Front Elevation, Right Side Elevation, Left Side Elevation, Rear Elevation
- I-F 514, 1915 (Map-case Folder 33)
  Project Description: House for W. T. Anderson